[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During which war did the first known pandemic take place?  It dates back to 430 BC.", "correct_answer": "The Peloponnesian War", "incorrect_answers": ["The Punic Wars", "The Persian Wars", "The Trojan War"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who stars as Danny Archer, the protagonist of the movie Blood Diamond?", "correct_answer": "Leonardo DiCaprio", "incorrect_answers": ["Matt Damon", "Brad Pitt", "Richard Gere"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What scientific term denotes body hair?", "correct_answer": "Androgenic hair", "incorrect_answers": ["Somatic hair", "All of these", "Puberty hair"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1994 John starred in a comedy film  about the adventures of a very wealthy child. What was the name of this movie that starred Macauley Caulkin, Ed Herrmann, Ben Stein, and Mike McShane?", "correct_answer": "Richie Rich", "incorrect_answers": ["Scrooge McDuck", "Misplaced Mansion", "Trading Places"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Jor-El, the biological father of Superman in the 1978 Superman movie?", "correct_answer": "Marlon Brando", "incorrect_answers": ["Glenn Ford", "Ned Beatty", "Nelson Leigh"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Katie Hnida?", "correct_answer": "The first female to play NCAA Division 1 football", "incorrect_answers": ["The first female to be a  professional boxer", "The first  American female to ride on the Space Shuttle", "The first female Prime Minister of Ecuador"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What have raccoons been mostly hunted for throughout history?", "correct_answer": "Their fur", "incorrect_answers": ["Their bones", "Their meat", "Their fat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1883 Otto Lilienthal became the first person to successfully fly this type of aircraft.", "correct_answer": "Glider", "incorrect_answers": ["Thermaclimber", "Graf Zeppelin", "Heavier than air balloon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the third-largest island on the planet, and it is also known as Kalimantan.", "correct_answer": "Borneo", "incorrect_answers": ["Bali", "Taiwan", "Java"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long is one day on planet Earth?", "correct_answer": "About 24 hours", "incorrect_answers": ["About 26 hours", "About 36 hours", "About 22 hours"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did the Catholic Church split with the Orthodox Church?", "correct_answer": "1054", "incorrect_answers": ["1645", "33", "1491"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the next number in the following sequence: 42, 48, 54, __?", "correct_answer": "60", "incorrect_answers": ["64", "50", "58"]}]